netfunda.com 2013-06-23

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how our website ‘[http://www.netfunda.com](http://www.netfunda.com/)’ uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website.

Netfunda Technologies is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. While using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.

**Gathering information**

  * Name and job title
  * Contact information including email address
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer 

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping. 
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services. 
  * We may periodically send promotional emails **** about new products, special offers or other information.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, **** we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Links**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and these sites are not governed by this privacy statement.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Netfunda Technologies may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of [http://www.netfunda.com](http://www.netfunda.com/) website after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

**Questions or Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please e-mail us at [info@netfunda.com](mailto:info@netfunda.com) 

**Registration and Use of Personal Information**

Registration is not required in order to use or access this website. However, this site may make forums, blogs, custom applications or similar available to its users. You may be required to register for these features, particularly if you wish to leave comments or provide articles.

If you do register, and in the process provide us with personally identifiable information, rest assured that any such information you provide will not be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent.

Please note that if you post comments etc on this site, any personally identifiable information you provide in those comments, collated and used by anyone viewing them.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, legal process served on our website.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
